# **James Johnson**

Junior Game Designer focusing on UX, Level and Gameplay Design. Experienced with an array of tools and engines for use in 2D and 3D game applications. Well-versed in software and tooling such as C#, Photoshop, Maya/Blender and more. Strong foundations in Project Management and teamwork roles.

Phone:

+44 7907477840

E-Mail:

james-aaron-johnson@outlook.com

Linkedin:

<u>linkedin.com /in/james-aaron-johnson/</u>

**Portfolio:** 

james-aaron-johnson.github.io/projects

### **Practical Skills**

- Project Management
- Games Design
- Gameplay Scripting
- 3D Design and Modelling
- Prototype Development
- Agile Methodology
- QA & Gameplay Testing

## **Tooling Skills**

- Unity Engine
- Unreal 4 Engine
- C# and .NET Framework
- Photoshop
- Blender / Maya
- Substance Painter

## **Experience**

09/2017 to 06/2020

#### Student Rep and Mentor - Solent University, Southampton

- Work with faculty to help guide goals of learning and keep the courses up to date with industry.
- Work in a professional cross-department setting and discuss issues such as financial, technological and management constraints to help Improve courses.
- Managed a mentorship program to help students with work and co-develop teaching materials with lecturers.
- Interface with local games industry to help gain insight to what should be taught and addressed in courses.

10/2015 to 06/2016

#### Audio Technician - Penwith College, Penzance

- Helped setup and organize live audio events such as theatre productions and concerts.
- In charge of audio balancing and mixing of live production audio.
- Worked closely with production managers to understand needs of artists and production vision.

03/2013 to 08/2014

#### **Event Organizer – Penwith College, Penzance**

- Interface with local establishments to help host musical events for college.
- Oversaw setup and hosting of events for college gigs as well as gained skills in management.

## **Education**

2017-2020

BA: Computer Games Design Solent University, Southampton

2014-2016

BTEC Level 3: Computer Games Technology Penwith College, Penzance

2012-2014

BTEC Level 3: Music Technology and Production Penwith College, Penzance